Julian Escontrias

2121 N. Jones Blvd. #285, Las Vegas, NV 89108 Contact: (702) 610-3514 | Email: <u>iescontr@techie.com</u>

IT professional with successful experience in the information technology field. Proficient in hardware and software maintenance. A solid track record of providing timely positive response to requests regarding computer related assistance. A deep understanding of the general organizational confidentiality policies associated with a I.T. specialist position.

Skills

Operating Systems: MS Windows Legacy and 10, Unix, Linux, OS X, IOS

Hardware: Dell, HP. Lenovo, Mac

Languages: Visual Basic, C, C++, SQL

Software: Office 365, Chrome, Outlook, Acrobat

Experience

June 2020 - PRESENT

Synoptek, Henderson, NV - Support Engineer

- Help desk Support for College of Southern Nevada Faculty/Staff and Students
- Desktop imaging and software support
- Work with SCCM, Datto RMM, Autotask ticketing system.

January 2020 - April 2020

United Parcel Service (UPS), Henderson NV - Technical/Customer Support

- Seasonal Employment
- Provide Technical Support for Website issues

November 2018 - December 2019

CG Technology - Las Vegas, NV - Technical Support

- Installation & configuration of a CG Technology's computer hardware and applications.
- Provide Phone Support for sport book staff and administration.
- Suport of the CG sportbook app for Android and IOS devices.

Experience

August 2016 - November 2019

Holo Discovery - Las Vegas, NV - Staff Support Associate

- Operate printing, binding, and scanning equipment
- Provide on-call technical support
- Assist in completion of print orders

January 2015 - July 2016

EWA Warrior Services - Fort Bliss, TX - Engineering Technician II

- Field exercise support of systems under testing including setup to breakdown of system
- Use of hand tools and multimeter for diagnostics of system under test
- Software and firmware updates of system during the testing event.

Education

Bachelor of Science Major: Computer Science/Minor: Mathematics

New Mexico State University, Las Cruces, NM